[{"answer": "Did I fuck", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You got a bird", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What? I can't hear you babe", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I'll find it when I get home", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I want to start getting stuff ready for next week", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "It's all right babe I'll get it", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I'll find it when I get home", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Jasmine, I'll get it when I get home", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "It's all right babe I'll get it", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Babe it's fine, I'll get it down", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Jasmine, I'll get it when I get home", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " I'LL FIND THE FUCKING THING WHEN I GET HOME", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Mum and dads", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Just do it", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You owe me money", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "YOU OWE ME MY FUCKING MONEY", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Tell it to the police, and I'll tell", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Fuck off, my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "How you been, alright", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Yeah, I'm alright", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "We don't need one", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "We'll get taxis. 41", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "How are we gonna get about with two kids", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "It'll be cheaper to get a hire car", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "We'll get taxis. 41", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Jasmine, we're not getting a hire car", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Jasmine, we're not getting a hire car", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What do you mean", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Don't ruin this for me, my friend", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Don't ruin this holiday for me", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Did anyone say anything", "docId": "Shifty.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I dunno, about me", "qsentId": 32}]